designmynight.com 2019-04-27

# Privacy Policy | DesignMyNight

## About Us

DesignMyNight is owned by Access UK Limited. It is a company incorporated in England and Wales, (no. 2343760) and whose registered address is Access UK Ltd., The Old School, Stratford St. Mary, Colchester, Essex, CO7 6LZ, United Kingdom. VAT no. GB 108221356.

## How we use your information

Access UK Ltd is a Processor of customer information and we take your privacy seriously.

Our Legal basis for processing client data is Contractual for the following activities

  * We receive data uploaded to the service by users where it is stored in a cloud environment or on premise in accordance with the options selected by customers.  Users may instruct the service to share some or all of the data with other users or groups/classes of users.
  * We process the customer’s personal data to enable them to access and use the service, provide support and maintenance services
  * We use personal information to communicate with clients in relation to service announcements, and product/service information.
  * We use personal information to send Customer Feedback information following visits and bookings
  * We use personal information to conduct Customer Surveys

Our legal basis for processing client data is Legitimate interest for the following activities:

  * Sending offers, sharing news and events and information regarding any purchases or bookings

Your data will be processed in line with the [Principles](https://ico.org.uk/for-organisations/guide-to-the-general-data-protection-regulation-gdpr/principles/) and [Rights](https://ico.org.uk/for-organisations/guide-to-the-general-data-protection-regulation-gdpr/individual-rights/) of The General Data Protection regulation.

You also have the right to withdraw consent where it has been provided and we will no longer send you information related to those subjects, which may mean you cannot not be informed about our latest events, offers and venues.

## Disclosure

We also use MailChimp for communications. They are located in the USA but they have certified to the [EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework](https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt0000000TO6hAAG&status=Active) and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and are therefore deemed as having adequate controls by the EU supervisory authority for GDPR

Your information will not otherwise be transferred out of the European Union without your prior consent; we will not share your personal data.

Your information will not be transferred out of the European Union without your prior consent; we will not share your personal data. 

By subscribing to our newsletter, this will mean receiving our weekly newsletters that include a "Top 5 events of the week", "Weekly round up" "Lightbulb" and  "Top 5 things this weekend" 

## Storage & Disposal

Your information will be stored in an encrypted database in the EEA and will be retained for 6 years. However you may ask for this to be deleted in accordance with the Rights of the GDPR by contacting [Information.Security@theaccessgroup.com](mailto:Information.Security@theaccessgroup.com) 

## Cookies

When you visit our website, we may automatically collect non-personal information about you, such as the type of browser you use and the way you arrived at our website (either a direct visit or via some referring website). The collection of this information may involve the use of cookies and web beacons. A web beacon is a small graphic image placed on a web page that is designed to allow us to monitor traffic on the website. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your computer's hard drive by your web browser when you first visit the website.

You cannot be identified from the information collected in this way on its own and it is only used to assist us in providing an effective service on our website and to collect broad demographic information for aggregate use and to improve the website.

Most browsers accept cookies automatically. You can erase or block cookies from your computer if you want to, but certain services may not work correctly or as fast or at all if you set your browser not to accept cookies

## Contact Information

Our Information Security/ Data Protection Manager can be contacted at - [Information.Security@theaccessgroup.com](mailto:Information.Security@theaccessgroup.com) 

Tel: 01206 32 13 14

Further information relating to GDPR can be found on our Client Portal [here](https://access-support.force.com/Support/s/gdpr-hub)

**Important note:** If you feel we have not processed your data in accordance with the Principles and Rights of the individual under GDPR, please contact [Information.Security@theaccessgroup.com](mailto:Information.Security@theaccessgroup.com) or you may also lodge a complaint with the [Information Commissioners Office](https://ico.org.uk/concerns/)

____ London newsletter 

Get weekly inspiration straight to your inbox! Get 250 (£2.50) reward points if you sign up now.

By entering your email address you agree to our [terms and conditions](https://www.designmynight.com/terms-and-conditions "Terms") and [privacy policy](https://www.designmynight.com/privacy-policy "Privacy Policy").

Congratulations, you have subscribed!

You should start seeing new bars, offers and openings in your inbox soon!

Congratulations, you have subscribed!

We've noticed you haven't signed up with us.

Get on board for exclusive discounts and money off the best events.

Signup

You should start seeing new bars, offers and openings in your inbox soon!
